http://www.berglundins.com/privacy-statement/

Privacy Statement | Berglund Insurance Agency | Utah
801.494.7400
HomePersonalAuto InsuranceHome InsuranceHealthcare- Individual/FamilyMedicareBoat InsuranceMotorcycle InsuranceATV InsuranceCommercialTow Truck InsuranceHomeowner Associations InsuranceWorkers CompensationHealth – Group/EmployerCommercial Auto InsuranceContractors InsuranceTire Dealer InsuranceBusiness Owner’s PolicyRecommended ProsOur CompanyContact UsMake a PaymentLoginCustomer LoginAgent LoginHomePersonalAuto InsuranceHome InsuranceHealthcare- Individual/FamilyMedicareBoat InsuranceMotorcycle InsuranceATV InsuranceCommercialTow Truck InsuranceHomeowner Associations InsuranceWorkers CompensationHealth – Group/EmployerCommercial Auto InsuranceContractors InsuranceTire Dealer InsuranceBusiness Owner’s PolicyRecommended ProsOur CompanyContact UsMake a PaymentLoginCustomer LoginAgent Login
Privacy StatementUpdated: 2/22/2019 1. Acknowledgement & Acceptance of Terms
Berglund Insurance Agency is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy statement sets forth our current privacy practices with regard to the information we collect when you or your computer interacts with our website. By accessing the Berglund Insurance Agency website, you acknowledge and fully understand the Berglund Insurance Agency privacy statement and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described herein.  2. Participating Merchant Policies
Related services and offerings with links from this website, including vendor sites, have their own privacy statements that can be viewed by clicking on the corresponding links within each respective website. Online merchants and others who participate in Berglund Insurance Agency services are encouraged to participate in industry privacy initiatives and to take a responsible attitude toward consumer privacy. Since we do not have direct control over the policies or practices of participating merchants and other third parties, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or contents of those sites. We recommend and encourage you to always review the privacy policies of merchants and other third parties before providing any personal information or completing any transaction with such parties.  3. Information We Collect and How We Use It
Berglund Insurance Agency collects certain information from and about its users in three ways: directly from web server logs, the user’s input and with cookies.  Web Server Logs
When you visit our website, we may track information to administer the site and analyze its usage. Examples of information we may track include:Your internet protocol addressThe browser and type of computer you useNumber of links you click within the siteState or country from which you accessed the siteDate and time of your visitName of your internet service providerWeb page/link you arrived fromPages you viewed on the site Use of Cookies
Berglund Insurance Agency may use cookies to personalize or enhance your user experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to save you time. For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a site, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of delivering relevant content and eases site navigation by providing and saving your preferences and login information, as well as providing personalized functionality. Berglund Insurance Agency reserves the right to share aggregated site statistics with partner companies, but does not allow other companies to place cookies on this website, unless there is a temporary, overriding customer value (such as merging into a site that relies on third-party cookies). You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline them. If you reject cookies by changing your browser settings, be aware that doing so may disable some functionality of this site. Personal Information Use
Visitors to our website can register for and purchase Berglund Insurance Agency services. When you register, we will request some personal information such as name, address, email, telephone number and/or facsimile number, account number or other relevant information. If you are purchasing a service, we will request financial information. Any financial information we collect is used only to bill you for the services you purchased. If you purchase by credit card, this information may be forwarded to your credit card provider. For other types of registrations, we will ask for the relevant information. You may also be asked to disclose personal information to us so that we can provide assistance and information to you. We will not disclose personally identifiable information we collect from you to third parties without your permission, except to the extent necessary, including:Fulfilment of your requests for servicesOur protection from liabilityResponse to legal processes or compliance with lawsIn connection with a merger, acquisition or liquidation of the company 4. Use of Web Beacons or GIF Files
Berglund Insurance Agency’s web pages may contain electronic images known as web beacons–sometimes also called single-pixel gifs–that allow Berglund Insurance Agency to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. Berglund Insurance Agency may include web beacons in promotional email messages or newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. Some of these web beacons may be placed by third-party service providers to help determine the effectiveness of advertising campaigns or email communications. These web beacons may be used to place a persistent cookie on your computer. This allows the service provider to recognize your computer each time you visit certain pages or emails and compile anonymous information in relation to those page views. This, in turn, enables us and our service providers to learn which advertisements and emails bring you to our website, and how you subsequently use the site. Berglund Insurance Agency prohibits web beacons from being used to collect or access personally identifiable information.  5. Links from this Website
We do not monitor or review the content of other parties’ websites, which may be linked from this site. Opinions expressed or material appearing on such websites is not necessarily shared nor endorsed by Berglund Insurance Agency and should not be regarded as published by Berglund Insurance Agency. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of all sites with which they interact. You should evaluate the security and trustworthiness of any other site connected to this site, or accessed by yourself, before disclosing any personal information. Berglund Insurance Agency will not accept any responsibility for loss or damage in whatever manner, howsoever caused, resulting from your disclosure to third parties of personal information. 6. Changes to this Statement
Berglund Insurance Agency maintains discretion to update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the “updated” date at the top of this page. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates. 7. Contacting UsIf you have questions regarding our privacy statement, its implementation, failure to adhere to this privacy statement or our general practices, please send comments to: Berglund Insurance Agency1881 W Traverse Pkwy, Ste E #203
Lehi, UT 84043
(801) 494-7400
(801) 921-5495
Service@BerglundInsurance.com Berglund Insurance Agency will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly respond and resolve any problem or question.
IMPORTANT LINKS
Home
Personal Insurance
Commercial Insurance
Recommended Professionals
Our Company
Contact Us
Make a Payment
Berglund Insurance. All rights reserved. Privacy Statement.Mail to: Berglund Insurance, Inc.1881 W Traverse PkwySte. E #203Lehi, UT 84043
×
